Hello everyone, this is Grass Shoes.
This is Old Hua,
and then what?
We're still waiting
for a few days of express delivery here.
Bought a little chicken oil and chicken green
Get ready to do
a maintenance on this car.
Because,
um,
if you leave Kunming,
It's
inconvenient to shop in the back of this
Then
I'm going to go to Tibet and Xinjiang.
Well,
what about this phase?
I'm going to tell you a little bit about this.
Because recently this exercise sub-travel
Well,
a lot about this topic.
That is to say, some of my own
Personal experience of
my this
Travel to Southeast Asia
mainly takes place in
Others are on their way to Africa
And then,
um,
it went through this.
Vietnam
Cambodia Thailand
Sunny Lanka These
Southeast Asian Countries
First and foremost, I'm most concerned
Everyone is a safety issue
Safety issues have been a problem
for me for more than a decade
For more than a decade of traveling,
Say the biggest one
The safety issue is that it happened in Malaysia
robbed in Malaysia in 1919
And then, it
was a robbery of one of my phones.
That was because I went to that
Malaysia is the one to go to
The black area,
that's the place.
It's just an unsafe area.
And then this happened.
Yeah,
but when I went to the police,
The cops said they didn't even dare go to that place.
Speaking of which, if you're traveling outside,
First
of all, because in every country, he
One language and this.
Lockdown habits and
all sorts of laws.
Everything is different
from everything else
And then,
so what,
each and every
each and every one of these possible
Maybe every one of these is different.
will create some problems.
So,
um, if you're traveling outside,
is that you have to be good before you go.
Plenty of power.
Well, that would avoid
Causes a lot of unnecessary trouble
So, but I'm in Malaysia
It's a place called Sandagan.
Because I'm going around for a walk.
And then there was a bag on the back.
And then take the phone and the dried fish.
Because I have fish in my bag. Why?
Just walking and playing.
It's a normal walk on the road.
It's a so-called black area.
And then that place's
Well,
the demographics of those places are quite complicated.
I heard they're all illegal immigrants, a little more.
Anyway, it's just being a
One by one, production is very
is to be toughened by a strong man
That strong man is useless for my one
Uh,
just take the dried fish, and then what? Just start.
Just start attacking me
And then I took my
Then he grabbed my phone.
I was also looking backwards
As soon as he snatched the phone away,
was to take my phone away from me.
I ran away,
and then I chased after it.
And then we didn't catch up.
Later, I passed the money on this mobile phone
I got him back. How did I get him back?
Because the person in this
place is the one who stole my mobile phone
He's quite tall.
Then the locals knew him.
But, uh, also through
However, that is, through a local
is an elderly person.
He said he could help me get my phone back.
It costs a lot of money
Later, this person who robbed me actually came with a swagger
And then, just so I can pay for it,
Get my phone back.
Because I have a lot of pictures and stuff on my phone.
Spend about 50 linen
Probably just as much.
Less than $100 should
This is a bit of luck.
Then I went to the police station and called the police.
The police department
says this about their people, they all
I just don't want to go to that place
It's like there's too much of this.
So, the most important thing is that you go to a place
Uh, go a little bit safely.
Because in my more than ten years of traveling,
Why did this happen?
is what happens in a city.
Because all my bad things happen in the city.
In the country, I...
Usually speaking, poor travelers like me
Usually a little more time on the road
So it's usually some very biased places to go
Somewhere in the countryside or something.
Of course, it is not excluded that there will be other
Something unexpected happened
Uh, you,
including me, in Africa.
I've been to some pretty biased places.
It's basically fine.
In fact, the most important security issue
They all come from people.
And then,
so on the outside, one is for you to go.
Go somewhere to get to know
and then to the local one.
Also for you is one of the people contacted in the clouds
A defense consciousness ah
Regardless of who you're traveling with
Or is it better to say that the people outside
Everyone must have a psychological awareness of defense
Because
people are popular.
Then if it's really wrong, no one can do it for you.
I basically live in a tent a bit more for all these years
And then, how many of these daughters-in-law are there?
Uh,
but nothing bad happened.
Because of me,
when the big account is bombing camp,
The more biased you choose, the better.
The more no-one, the better.
The safer it
is, so what now?
And I don't have much of a nightlife either.
I smoke and drink again, and neither do I.
So basically these
It just eliminates some big insecure factors.
A lot of people like to go at night these days.
Go play in the city
And then,
in this case, the accident will be a little more
Probably more likely
In addition, about
In fact, every country, no matter what country it is,
It's going to have something bad in it.
So, no, no, no, absolutely safe place.
and then some information about some of the reviews for the evening
Maybe some of them he hasn't even been abroad.
So you guys have to have your own.
Discernment is the idea that you have to be yourself.
No, don't be swayed by these things.
A lot of things on the Internet, he's purposeful.
Tell me about this cost-effective, cost-effective,
To be called cost-effective is to make a comparison with our country
And then,
because my words mean to me, in fact, I spend very little in any country I go to.
I don't live in a hotel, and then I eat
Eating is easy, too. Most cities cook their own meals.
is to look at the scenery on the road a little bit
Like this year, because the global economy as a whole is not good.
And then
you look at this Thailand where prices are now going up.
However, compared to domestic
It's better if it's cost-effective.
When I was in Thailand, when that other person was passing through Thailand,
I ate that risotto, but it was only 30 Thai dollars.
30 Thai pigs, this is me
It's only about 6 yuan
Especially inexpensive.
It's definitely more than that now.
Anyway, no matter where you travel, then
Be sure to get to know some of the local
is that where you go, you must carry out an understanding strategy.
In a network where information is well developed, you can
Anything you want to know can be found online. Be well-prepared.
Then try to go out less at night
Don't go to some like me
Well, I never go to these bars or anything.
But you, so everyone has to act for their own sake.
Just pay the bill.
Anyway, what we do is
No matter where you are traveling, whether you are at home or abroad
Be careful of your own safety
After all, safety outside the home is always the first priority.
All right, that's all for today's video.
Today, this Kumin is holding a marathon
Now put the wind on this road
I can't get out. This road is already bubbling marathons.
I can't get out of this right now. Right here, watching them run marathons.
Bye-bye.